<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
  <title>Stanislav Kozin&#39; Homepage</title>
  <link>https://kozin.cc/categories/</link>
  <description>Recent content in Categories on Stanislav Kozin&#39; Homepage</description>
  <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
  <language>en</language>
    
        <atom:link href="https://kozin.cc/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  
  
  <item>
    <title>My Salvation Testimony</title>
    <link>https://kozin.cc/testimony/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 19:49:53 -0600</pubDate>
    
    <guid>https://kozin.cc/testimony/</guid>
    <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Bible says in &lt;em&gt;1Pet 3:15 &amp;ldquo;But sanctify the Lord God in your hearts: and be ready always to give an answer to every man that asketh you a reason of the hope that is in you with meekness and fear:&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story is the story of my salvation, and I pray to the Lord Jesus Christ that it will lead us to the salvation of your soul.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;orthodoxy&#34;&gt;Orthodoxy&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was born in 1982 in ex-USSR, in a typical soviet family where God was not mentioned at all, maybe a cussword or a filler word. I never heard my parents mention God or the Lord Jesus Christ. Even though they would go to an Orthodox church once in a while: Easter, someone&amp;rsquo;s wedding or funeral. For all my life I have been sure that they were practical atheists, or as I called them, &amp;ldquo;Orthodox atheists.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My grandmother, on the other hand, was a Russian Orthodox who would go to church almost every Sunday and would keep all the major feasts. When I was several months old, the decision was made to baptize me in the Russian Orthodox church.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>What if you die today?</title>
    <link>https://kozin.cc/salvation/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 19:43:04 -0600</pubDate>
    
    <guid>https://kozin.cc/salvation/</guid>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;One day you are going to die. And the most important question that should be answered is, 

&lt;span  class=&#34;info-red&#34;&gt;&#34;Where are you going when you die?&#34;&lt;/span&gt; Notice, there is no if in this quesion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;a&#34;&gt;A&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;b&#34;&gt;B&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;c&#34;&gt;C&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>About Stanislav Kozin</title>
    <link>https://kozin.cc/about/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 17:49:46 -0600</pubDate>
    
    <guid>https://kozin.cc/about/</guid>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;N.B. This page is under development. I am constantly updating the page. Thank you for understanding&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Stanislav. I was born physically in 1982 (please read my &lt;a href=&#34;https://kozin.cc/testimony&#34;&gt;salvation testimony&lt;/a&gt;) in a country that does not exist anymore. I was born in a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Karaganda&#34;&gt;city&lt;/a&gt; that became a meme in ex-USSR and a go to answer to the question, &amp;ldquo;Where?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
	&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://kozin.cc/images/karaganda.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Karaganda&#34; style=&#34;width:450px;&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Karaganda&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was 10 years old my parents bought me my first computer a &lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commodore_64&#34;&gt;Commodore 64&lt;/a&gt; a very useless piece of hardware outside of the United States and Western Europe. But I spent a lot of type behind that &amp;ldquo;light-brown&amp;rdquo; keyboard writing my first lines of code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;10 PRINT &amp;#34;HELLO WORLD&amp;#34;
20 GO TO 10
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then I fell in love with technology and computers in general. There was something magical about telling a computer what to do and figuring out why didn’t it do what it was supposed to do or what you thought it was supposed to do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1994, when I was 14 years old, my family moved from Kazakhstan to Russia, and we settled in a small town on the Black Sea coast which became the capital of the 2014 Winter Olympic Games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
	&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://kozin.cc/images/sochi.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Sochi&#34; style=&#34;width:450px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As long as I live, I always wanted to live in the United States of America. I don’t know why. I had never been to the States, didn’t speak English at all, and everything I knew about the States was from the movies. (I know) And in 2013, when I was 30 years old, God gave me this opportunity, and my dream became true. On May 31, 2013, an immigration officer said the phrase I had been waiting for, &amp;ldquo;Welcome to the United States of America.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
	&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://kozin.cc/images/aeroflot_usa.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Aeroflot SVO LAX&#34; style=&#34;width:450px;&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;This plane brought me to the United States of America&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior moving to the States I worked as a product manager for one of the bigger cellular carrier in Russia. It was a nice and very interesting field but I always wanted to work in IT, work with computers and try that &amp;ldquo;itching&amp;rdquo; &lt;em&gt;What if&lt;/em&gt; question on practice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I became a Quality Assurance Engineer. In my carrier as a Quality Assurance Engineer I have worked for very small startups in Silicon Valley as well as for the Fortune 500 corporations testing everything from the Network to mobile applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to High Tech I am fan of ice-hockey and adventure motorcycles.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <title>Books I Recommend</title>
    <link>https://kozin.cc/books/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 17:49:46 -0600</pubDate>
    
    <guid>https://kozin.cc/books/</guid>
    <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-monarch-of-the-books&#34;&gt;The Monarch of The Books&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you put a gun to my head and tell me that I can have only one book and one only without any hesitation and second thought, I would tell you, “The Holy Bible AV1611!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;
	&lt;center&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://store.kjv1611.org/bible-mountain-postcard/&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://kozin.cc/images/bible_mountain.jpeg&#34; style=&#34;height:450px;&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Bible Mountain by Dr. Peter S. Ruckman&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;2022&#34;&gt;2022&lt;/h2&gt;
</description>
  </item>
  
  </channel>
</rss>
